爸爸走了
Look, dad's gone now.
我们得继承他的遗志
We have to carry out his legacy.
那就是
And that means hunting down.
能猎杀多少凶鬼恶灵杀多少
as many evil sons of bitches as we possibly can.
（忆往昔）
我死了吗
Did I die?
你为我出卖了灵魂吗
Did you sell your soul for me?
你还有多久
How long you get?
一年
One year.
你不该那么做的
You shouldn't have done that.
看来要换我救你了
Guess I gotta save your ass for a change.
什么样的刀能杀恶魔
What kind of blade can kill a demon?
昨天的话 我会说没有这种东西
Yesterday, I'd have said there was no such thing.
那无名小妞是谁
Who was that masked chick?
你遇见过一个叫戈登·沃克的人吗
You ever run across a guy named Gordon Walker?
他对他身边的所有人和事物都是个威胁
He is dangerous to everyone and everything around him.
这个恶魔告诉我
This demon tells me.
他们有士兵会在这场将到来的战争里作战
they have soldiers to fight in this coming war.
人类 为地狱而战
Humans fighting on hell's side.
我知道了
I know…
关于萨姆能看到幻象
about Sam's visions.
我什么都知道了
I know everything.
你弟弟是我的目标
And your brother's fair game.
戈登接下来几年里
Gordon should be reaching for the soap.
肯定要捡肥皂了
for the next few years at least.
告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you are!
你是个恶魔
You're a demon.
我来找你是因为我想帮你
I'm here because I wanna help you.
你能给我…
What could you possibly…?
我能帮你救你哥哥
I could help you save your brother.
（如今）
胳膊抬起来
Lift your arms.
下一个
Next.
是真的
It's true.
怀俄明州的一个魔鬼之门被打开了
A Devil's Gate was opened in Wyoming.
很大的门
Big.
有圣赫勒拿那么大
Saint Helena's big.
无法确切知道有多少恶魔逃出来了
There's no solid fix on how many demons got out.
但有上百个 一支大军
But it's in the hundreds. An army.
萨姆·温彻斯特当时在场 是吧
Sam Winchester was there, wasn't he?
我跟一个认识鲍比·辛格一个朋友的人谈过
Talked to a guy who knows a guy who knows Bobby Singer.
是的
and yeah.
看来大门被打开时
Looks like the Winchesters were at ground zero.
温家兄弟就在当场
when the gate was popped.
但辛格说 他们是去阻止开门的
But Singer said they went in there to stop it.
鲍比不像以前那么敏锐了
Bobby's edge ain't what it used to be.
萨姆现在能骗他相信任何鬼话
Sam could have him believing anything by now.
听着 戈登 据传言
Listen, Gordon, as far as talk goes,
萨姆·温彻斯特没问题
Sam Winchester checks out.
只是个猎人
He's a hunter, that's all.
是吗
That's all?
库布里克
Kubrick…
我都不确定他是人类
I'm not even sure he's human.
你觉得我疯了吗
Think I'm crazy?
我六个月前就告诉你战争要来了
I told you there was a war coming six months ago.
看看你身边吧
Take a look around.
战争是来了
It's here.
现在我跟你说这小子是这场战争的一部分
Now I'm telling you this boy is a part of it.
找到他 库布里克
Track him down, Kubrick.
你也会明白的
You'll come to see it too.
萨姆·温彻斯特必须死
Sam Winchester must die.
[邪恶力量 第3季第3集]
因为她是恶魔
Because demon, that's why.
你一发现这个露比是个恶魔
Because the second you find out this Ruby chick is a demon…
就该去拿圣水 不是跟她闲聊
you go for the holy water. You don't chat.
我们没闲聊 迪恩
No one was chatting, Dean.
是吗 那你怎么没把她送回地狱
Yeah? Then why didn't you send her ass back to hell?
因为 她说她或许能帮我们
Because… Because she said she might be able to help us out.
怎么帮
How?
不 说真的 萨姆 她怎么可能帮得上我们
No, really, Sam, how? How could she possibly help us?
她说她能帮你
She told me she could help you, okay?
帮你摆脱十字路口交易
Help you out of the Crossroads deal.
你是什么毛病 她在撒谎
What is wrong with you, huh? She's lying.
你知道吧
You gotta know that, don't you?
她知道你的弱点是我
She knows what your weakness is. It's me.
她还说了什么
What else did she say?
哥们
Dude?
没有了
Nothing.
没有了 好吗
Nothing, okay?
听着 我又不傻 迪恩
Look, I'm not an idiot, Dean.
我不是说要信任她
I'm not talking about trusting her.
我是说要利用她
I'm talking about using her.
我们在打仗 是吧
I mean, we're at war, right?
我们对敌人完全不了解
And we don't know jack about the enemy.
我们不知道他们在哪
We don't know where they are,
我们不知道他们在做什么
we don't know what they're doing,
我们都不知道他们想要什么
I mean, hell we don't even know what they want.
这个露比
Now, this Ruby girl.
知道的信息 我们自己绝对查不出来
knows more than we will ever find out on our own.
是的 这是冒险 我知道
Now, yes, it's a risk, I know that,
但我们必须冒险
but we need to take it.
你没事吧 你感觉还好吧
You're okay, right? I mean, you feeling okay?
我很好
Yes, I'm fine.
你干吗老问我这个
Why are you always asking me that?
不是我的
It's not mine.
也不是我的
Nope.
看看储物箱 是爸爸的
Check the glove compartment. It's Dad's.
- 爸爸的 - 对
- Dad's? - Yes.
我保持手机充满电 以防他的老熟人来电话
I keep it charged up in case any of his old contacts call.
喂
Hello?
对 我是埃德加·凯西
Yes, this is Edgar Cayce.
不不 别报警 我自己处理
No, no, no. Don't call the police. I'll handle this myself.
谢谢 你可以…
Thanks. You know, can you just,
你可以重新帮我锁好吗
can you just lock it back up for me?
太好了
Great.
我…我的记事簿不在手里
I… I don't have my book in front of me.
你可以把地址给我吗
Do you…? Do you have the address so I…?
好的 好 说吧
Sure. Okay. Go ahead.
好 多谢了
Right. Thanks a lot.
爸爸跟你说过他在一间仓库里有个集装箱吗
Dad ever tell you he kept a container at a storage place?
- 什么 - 在水牛城城外
- What? - Outside of Buffalo?
- 不会吧 - 是啊
- No way. - Yeah.
有人刚刚闯了进去
And someone just broke into it.
你并没有这个温彻斯特的什么实证
So you got no hard evidence on this Winchester guy?
你只是听信了戈登的直觉
You're just working off Gordon's instincts.
你跟戈登一起猎过魔吗
You ever hunt with Gordon?
没有
No.
我听说他很厉害
I heard he's good.
厉害
Good?
他是最厉害的 救过我好多次了
He's the best. Saved my ass more times than I can count.
如果他说萨姆·温彻斯特是危险人物
So if he says Sam Winchester is dangerous,
那我就相信他
I believe him.
他肯定会掩盖踪迹
He's gonna be covering his tracks.
不会好找的
Won't be easy to find.
据我能查到的 他三周前去过内布拉斯加
Last I got, puts him in Nebraska three weeks back.
这线索不新了
Not exactly a fresh lead.
他又不是隐形人 克雷迪
He ain't invisible, Creedy.
肯定有猎人知道点什么
Some hunter out there knows something.
我们挨个联系我们认识的人
So we start calling our contacts.
我们只需要走一回运
All we need is one break.
别碰我的耶稣
Don't play with my Jesus.
天啊
Man.
怎么了
What?
就是爸爸
Just Dad.
他和他的秘密
You know, him and his secrets.
跟他在一起那么久
Spend all this time with the guy,
可我们还是不怎么了解他
it's like we barely even know the man.
我们马上要了解到点什么了
Well, we're about to learn something.
恶魔止步
No demons allowed.
血
Blood.
看啊
Check this out.
闯进来的人被打中了
Whoever broke in here got tagged.
亲爱的老爸
Dear old Dad.
我看到两组靴印
I got two sets of boot treads here.
看来是两人作案
Looks like it was a two-man job.
被打中的那个
And our friend with the buckshot in him,
看来没被打死
looks like he kept walking.
怎么回事 爸爸会在这里工作吗
So, what's the deal? Dad would do work here or something?
还是生活得那么奢侈
Living the high life, as usual.
- 1995年的 - 不会吧
- 1995. - No way.
那是我的区足球锦标赛奖杯
That's my division championship soccer trophy.
真不敢相信他留下了这个
I can't believe he kept this.
是啊
Yes.
那可能是你最像个小男孩的时刻了
Probably the closest you ever came to being a boy.
是我的第一把锯断猎枪 我自己做的
It's my first sawed-off. I made it myself.
六年级
Sixth grade.
我去
Holy crap.
看这个 他还有地雷
Look at this, he had land mines.
他们没拿
Which they didn't take.
也没拿枪
Or the guns.
看来他们很清楚自己想要什么
I guess they knew what they were after, huh?
迪恩 看啊
Dean, check this out.
看到这些符号了吗
See these symbols?
那是束缚咒
That's binding magic.
这都是诅咒盒
These are curse boxes.
诅咒盒
Curse boxes.
那是用来把邪恶魔法困在里面的 是吧
Supposed to keep the evil mojo in, right?
- 就像潘多拉魔盒 - 对
- Kinda like the Pandora deal. - Yeah.
嗯 是建造来容纳诅咒物件魔力的
Yeah. They're built to contain the power of the cursed object.
爸爸的日记里是提到过好多东西
Dad's journal did mention a whole bunch of stuff, you know?
危险的被施咒的物品 魔物
Dangerous hexed items, fetishes.
- 可他没说过那些东西都哪去了 - 是啊
- He never did say where they ended up. - Yeah.
看来这里是他的有毒垃圾场
Well, this must be his toxic-waste dump.
有个盒子不见了
One box is missing.
好啊
Great.
或许他们没打开
Well, maybe they didn't open it.
来吧 伙计 我们把它打开
Come on, man. Let's open it.
别逼逼那破盒子了
Shut up about the damn box!
你看到现在的情况了没有
Do you see what's happening here?
我都要流血致死了
I'm literally bleeding to death.
- 我要打开它 - 格罗斯曼
- I'm gonna open it. - Grossman.
如果这玩意真挺值钱呢
Look, what if this is really worth something?
怎么 我们就该把这交给她吗
What, we should just hand it over to her?
冒险是我们冒的
We took all the risk.
韦恩 你还中枪了
Hell, Wayne, you got shot.
就为了几百块
And all for a lousy few hundred bucks.
我们自己卖掉里面的东西 能挣更多
Now, we could make more selling whatever it is ourselves.
开什么玩笑 开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me? Are you kidding me?
是只兔脚 是只兔脚 格罗斯曼
It's a rabbit's foot. It's a rabbit's foot, Grossman!
我要为只破兔脚而死了
I'm gonna die for a damn rabbit's foot.
好啊 又怎么了
Great. Now what?
福斯特
Foster.
听着 伙计们 不是我找事
Listen, guys, not to be a drag or nothing,
- 但这才大早上6点 - 好吧
- but it's 6:00 in the morning. - Right.
- 你们不能小点声吗 - 不
- Can't you keep it down? - No, we…
我们就是有点情况 抱歉
just got a situation here is all. Sorry.
你是怎么了
What the hell happened to you?
被猎枪打了
Shotgun happened to me.
- 格罗斯曼 - 嗯
- Grossman. - Yeah.
我水池下面有个医疗包
Under my sink, there's a medical kit.
再去烧点水
And get some water boiling.
好
Okay.
我在越南做过医护兵
I used to be an Army medic, you know, in Nam.
看来你今天走运了
So I guess this is your lucky day.
（康涅狄格州）
康涅狄格州 最后三位是880
Connecticut. Last three digits: 880.
对 就是它
Yup. That's it.
真不该不涂黑车牌
Should've blacked out their plates.
就停在监控范围内
before they parked in front of the security camera.
四个K
Four kings.
- 看到了吗 - 难以置信
- You see that? - Unbelievable.
嗯嗯
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
再发一次
Deal it up again.
红桃K
King of hearts?
红桃A
Ace of hearts.
同花大顺
Royal flush.
格罗斯曼 这是八手里第二个同花大顺了
Grossman, that's the second royal flush in eight hands.
对 这真好玩
Yeah, this is a lot of fun.
我输不了
I can't lose.
我真的输不了
I mean, really, I… I can't lose.
或许这玩意真好使
Maybe this thing really works.
你明白吗
You know what I'm saying?
告诉你 我们绝不能
I'll tell you one thing, there's no way in hell,
把它交给那个自命不凡的贱人
we're handing it over to that stuck-up bitch.
看看我们受了多少罪
Not after all we've been through.
走
Let's go.
我们走吧 我们去玩玩吧
Let's get out of here. Let's go have some fun.
别动 都别动
Freeze! Freeze! Nobody move!
别动
Don't move.
Don't move!
- 干什么 - 别动
- What is this? - Stop!
好了 把盒子给我们
All right, give us the box.
拜托告诉我你们没…
And please tell me that you didn't…
他们打开了
They did.
你们打开了
You opened it?
你们是警察吗
Are you guys cops, huh?
- 你们是警察吗 - 盒子里是什么
- Are you guys cops? - What was in the box?
是那个吗
Is that it, huh?
是吧
It was, wasn't it?
那是什么
What is that thing?
抱歉
Sorry.
迪恩
Dean.
我拿到了
I got it.
不 你没有
No, you don't.
该死
Damn!
萨姆
Sam!
好幸运
That was a lucky break.
那是兔脚吗
That a rabbit's foot?
好像是的
I think it is.
（比格森餐厅）
我在爸爸的日记里什么都没找到
I'm not finding anything on it in Dad's journal.
- 迪恩 拜托 - 怎么了
- Dean, come on. - What?
他可是拿我的枪对着你的头
That was my gun he was aiming at your head.
我的枪不会卡 所以那是好运气
My gun don't jam, so that was a lucky break.
更别提 他们还自己撞晕了 也是好运气
Not to mention them taking themselves out, also a lucky break.
来 刮开
Here. Scratch one.
来吧 萨姆 刮开赢奖
Come on, Sam. Scratch and win.
迪恩 这上面肯定有诅咒
Dean, it's gotta be cursed somehow.
否则爸爸也不会把它锁起来
Otherwise Dad wouldn't have locked it up.
1200美元
Twelve hundred dollars.
你刚赢了1200美元
You just won $1200.
我不知道 我不觉得它像诅咒呢
I don't know, man. Doesn't seem that cursed to me.
格罗斯曼
Grossman.
格罗斯曼 起来
Grossman, get up.
格罗斯曼
Grossman?
Grossman.
天啊
Man.
鲍比 我们又不知道
Now, look, Bobby, we didn't know.
你碰它了 该死 萨姆
You touched it? Damn it, Sam.
爸爸没跟我们提过这玩意
Well, Dad never told us about this thing.
你知道他在黑岩有个仓库吗
I mean, you knew about his storage place in Black Rock?
他的仓库吗 我知道
His lockup? Yeah, I knew.
那些诅咒盒还是我给他做的
Hell, I built those curse boxes for him.
听着 你的麻烦大了
Listen, you have got a serious problem.
那只兔脚可不是骗人的
That rabbit's foot ain't no dime-store notion.
那是真巫术
It's real Hoodoo.
- 很古老的 - 太棒了
- Old World stuff. - Awesome.
是一个巴吞鲁日巫女大概一百年前做的
Made by a Baton Rouge conjure woman about a hundred years ago.
好厉害的幸运符啊
It's a hell of a luck charm.
那不是幸运符 是诅咒
It's not a luck charm. It's a curse.
她是做来杀人的 萨姆
She made it to kill people, Sam.
你碰到它 它就属于你了
See, you touch it, you own it.
它属于你时 是啊 你会好运连连
You own it, sure, you get a run of good luck to beat the devil.
但等你丢了它 运气就逆转了
But you lose it, that luck turns.
急转直下 你一周内就会死
It turns so bad that you're dead inside a week.
那我就不弄丢它 鲍比
Well, so I won't lose it, Bobby.
每个人最终都会弄丢它
Everybody loses it.
那我们怎么打破诅咒
Well, then how do we break the curse?
我不知道你能不能打破
I don't know if you can.
我来翻翻我的藏书 再找人问问
Let me look through my library and make some calls.
等我消息吧
Just sit tight.
哥们
Dude,
我们赢到1.5万了
we're up 15 grand.
别担心 鲍比会找到办法打破诅咒的
Don't worry. Bobby will find a way to break it.
在此之前 我们去维加斯吧
Until then, I say we hit Vegas,
演一出《雨人》 你来演雨人
pull a little Rain Man. You can be Rain Man.
我们就按兵不动 等待鲍比再来电 好吗
Look, we lay low until Bobby calls back, okay?
两人桌 谢谢
Table for two, please?
恭喜
Congratulations!
是啊 好让人激动
Exciting, I know.
你们是比格森餐厅大家庭的
You are the one millionth guest…
第一百万位客人
of the Biggerson's Restaurant family!
恭喜
Congratulations.
好 你听到什么消息就联系我
Right. You hear anything, you give me a call.
我的联络人都打过了
Well, that clears my book.
消息传开了 现在我们等着吧
The word's out. Now we wait.
我们吃东西吧
Now we eat.
好主意
Good idea.
你想吃什么 我有各种罐头
What do you like? I got canned everything.
不 伙计 别在房车里吃
No, man. Not eating in the RV.
我知道个好地方
Look, I know a good place.
菜单花样多 服务好 气氛温馨
Wide menu, good service, homey atmosphere.
还有大蒜结
Garlic knots.
他们网站上有菜单
Menu's on their website.
鲍比是对的 这传说历史悠久
Bobby's right. This lore goes way back.
纯巫术
Pure Hoodoo.
不能随便找只兔子切腿
You can't just cut one off any rabbit.
必须在一个公墓里
It has to be in a cemetery,
在一个13日星期五的满月下
under a full moon, on a Friday the 13th.
从今往后
I say from now on…
我们只去有比格森餐厅的城市
we only go to places with Biggerson's.
要我给你续杯吗
Can I freshen you up?
嗯 好
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 我来擦擦吧 - 没事
- Let me wipe up. - No worries.
不要紧 我来吧
That's okay. That's… I got it.
不麻烦的
It's no trouble, really.
好吧
Okay.
抱歉了
Sorry about that.
没事
It's all right.
哥们
Dude,
如果你这辈子能走桃花运
if you were ever gonna get lucky.
闭嘴吧
Shut up.
天啊
Jeez.
抱歉
Sorry.
这怎么能算好事
How was that good?
该死
Son of a bitch.
快走
Come on.
你真蠢
You suck.
怎么 你的运气现在变坏了吗
So, what, now your luck turns bad?
看来是的
I guess.
不知道会多坏
Wonder how bad.
不错
Looks good.
我喜欢他们把整个洋葱丢进去炸
I like that, when they drop the whole onion in the fryer.
最近的一家
Nearest location…
你看到了吗
You seeing that?
看到了
Yes, I am.
再见了 朋友
Adiós, compadre.
天啊
Man.
你们还想怎样
What do you want?
听说你朋友的事了 真倒霉
Heard about your friend. That's bad luck.
滚蛋
Piss off.
我们知道有人雇了你们偷兔脚
We know someone hired you to steal the rabbit's foot.
一个女人
A woman.
是吗
Yeah?
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
因为她刚从我们手里偷走了它
Because she just stole it back from us.
听着 伙计 这事很严…
Listen, man, this is serio…
- 萨姆 你没事吧 - 我没事
- Sam, are you okay? - Yeah, I'm good.
告诉我们她叫什么
I want you to tell us her name.
去你妈
Screw you.
你的伙伴不是死于意外事故
It wasn't a freak accident that killed your partner.
什么
What?
是那个兔脚
It was the rabbit's foot.
你疯了
You're crazy, man.
你清楚我没疯
You know I'm not.
你看到它都做到什么了
You saw what happened, what it did.
各种巧合 运气
All the flukes, all the luck.
你失去兔脚后 运气便变坏
When you lose the foot, that luck goes sour.
那才是害死你朋友的
That's what killed your friend.
我弟弟就是下一个了
And my brother here is next.
谁知道之后还有多少无辜者会因此而死
And who knows how many more innocent people after that.
如果你不帮我们阻止它
Now, if you don't help us stop this thing,
那些人的死便要算在你头上
that puts those deaths on your head.
我会识人
Now, I can read people.
我知道
And I get it.
你是个贼 人渣 这没关系
You're a thief and a scumbag. That's fine.
但你不是杀人犯
But you're not a killer.
是不是
Are you?
没人看到他们去了哪边
No one saw which way they went.
而且因为免单 他们也没用信用卡
And their meal was free so there's no credit-card trail.
别担心 我们会找到他的
Don't worry, we'll find him.
你为什么那么确定
What makes you so sure?
因为这里面有更高力量在运作
Because there's a higher power at work here.
我现在知道了
I know it now.
喂
Hello?
迪恩 好消息
Dean, great news.
虽然不容易 但我找到个很厉害的净化咒
Wasn't easy, but I found a heavyweight cleansing ritual.
应该会好用
that should do the trick.
鲍比 那太好了 但萨姆…
Bobby, that's, uh, great. Except Sam…
- 萨姆丢了兔脚 - 什么
- Sam lost the foot. - He what?
鲍比 听着
Bobby, listen. Listen. This,
有个辣妹从他身上偷走了
this hot chick stole it from him.
真的 她25左右
I'm serious. She was in her mid 20s.
而且很厉害
And she was sharp, you know?
厉害到骗过了我们
Good enough with the con to play us.
她只跟她雇的人说了个名字
And she only gave the guy she hired a name,
可能也是假名
probably an alias or something.
是路易吉什么的
Luigi or something.
- 是卢戈西 - 卢戈西
- Lugosi. - Lugosi.
卢戈西
Lugosi?
Lugos…
该死 可能是贝拉
Crap. It's probably Bela.
贝拉·卢戈西（饰演吸血鬼德古拉的男演员）吗 还挺逗
Bela Lugosi? That's cute.
她真名叫贝拉·塔伯特
Bela Talbot's her real name.
跟她有过一两次交集
Crossed paths with her once or twice.
她知道兔脚的事
She knew about the rabbit's foot.
她是猎人吗
Is she a hunter?
才不是呢
Pretty frigging far from a hunter.
但她很熟悉这个领域
But she knows her way around the territory.
她之前出国了
She's been out of the country.
据我之前所知 她去了中东什么地方
Last I heard she was in the Middle East some place.
看来她回来了
Well, I guess she's back.
对你来说就很不幸了
Which means seriously bad luck for you.
好啊
Great.
但如果真是贝拉
But if it is Bela…
至少我或许认识知道去哪能找到她的人
at least I might know some folks who know where to find her.
谢谢 鲍比 再次感谢
Thanks, Bobby. Again.
照顾好你的弟弟吧 白痴
Just look out for your brother, you idiot.
怎么了
What?
我丢了只鞋
I lost my shoe.
（汽车旅馆）
好吧 鲍比 谢谢
All right, Bobby, thanks.
我们又欠你个人情
We owe you another one.
好了 鲍比打探到可靠消息
All right. Bobby's got it on pretty good authority.
这个贝拉住在皇后区
that this Bela chick lives in Queens.
我开车两小时就能过去
So it'll take me about two hours to get there.
那我们来这里干什么
So what are we doing then?
你 我的弟弟 要待在这里
You, my brother, are staying here…
因为我不希望你的噩运害死我们
because I don't want your bad luck getting us killed.
我该做什么啊 迪恩
What am I even supposed to do, Dean?
什么都不做 过来
Nothing. Nothing. Come here.
我不要你做任何事
I don't want you doing anything.
我要你坐在这里
I want you to sit right here…
一动别动 好吗
and don't move, okay?
别去开灯
Don't turn on the light.
别去关灯
Don't turn off the light.
连鼻子都别挠
Don't even scratch your nose.
（纽约市 皇后区）
因为我们说好的是150
Because you shook on 1.5.
那或许我该卖给别人
Well, maybe I should just take it somewhere else.
别威胁我 卢克
Don't threaten me, Luke.
尽管你名声在外 我并不怕你
Despite your reputation, you don't scare me.
很高兴你能这么想
Well, I'm glad you see it that way.
一小时后机场见
I'll see you at the airstrip in an hour.
（错误）
（回头）
你没拿小费就走了
You left without your tip.
拜托
Come on.
我都没…
I didn't… I wasn't…
把它还给我
You're gonna give it back.
亲爱的 我才不要
Sweetie. No, I'm not.
走着瞧吧
Yeah, we'll see.
贝拉 是吗
Bela, right?
对
That's right,
迪恩
Dean.
你知道那玩意有诅咒吧
You know the thing's cursed, don't you?
你想不到有些人会愿意为这种东西
You'd be surprised what some people would pay.
出多少钱
for something like that.
是吗
Really?
在这方面有个利润丰厚的市场呢
There's a lucrative market out there.
可以挣大钱
A lot of money to be made.
你们这些猎人 用各种护身符什么的
You hunters with all those amulets and talismans you use.
阻止可怕的怪物
to stop those big, bad monsters.
随便哪个
Any one of them.
都足够让你们的孙辈上大学
could put your children's children through college.
你知道真相
So you know the truth…
你知道外面有什么
about what's really going on out there.
你却做了这个
and this is what you decide to do with it?
做个贼
You become a thief?
我为特定客户获取一些独特的东西
I procure unique items for a select clientele.
嗯
Yeah.
贼
A thief.
不
No.
是神偷
A great thief.
他醒了
He's awake.
醒过来了吗
Back with us, eh?
我们都没碰你
We didn't even have to touch you.
你自己抽抽搭搭地撞昏了过去
You just went all spastic and knocked yourself out.
简直像看谐星杰瑞·刘易斯踩一堆摞起来的椅子
It was like watching Jerry Lewis ride a stacked chair.
你们是谁
Who are you?
你们想要什么…
What do you wa…?
我本以为是你朋友戈登派我来的
I used to think your friend Gordon sent me.
戈登
Gordon?
- 拜托 - 嗯
- Come on. - Yeah.
因为他叫我找到你
Because he asked me to track you down.
然后一枪崩了你
and put a bullet in your brain.
好啊 听上去像他的做派
Great. That sounds like him.
但是
But.
原来
as it turns out…
我是在执行上帝的使命
I'm on a mission from God.
贝拉 我弟弟 他碰了兔脚
Look, Bela, my brother, he touched the foot.
你夺走之后 他的好运就变成了…
And when you took it from him, his luck went from…
我清楚原理
I know how it works.
所以你知道他会死的 除非我们销毁它
So then, you know he's gonna die unless we can destroy it.
兔脚可以给你
You can have the foot.
但要150万美元
For 1.5 million.
好啊
Nice. Yeah.
等我联系下我的银行家
I'll just call my banker.
你怎么找到这玩意的
How did you even find the damn thing?
藏在那么隐蔽的仓库深处
Stuck in the back of some storage place, middle of nowhere?
我问了几个被它害死的人的鬼魂
I just asked a few of the ghosts of the people it had killed.
他们能感应到它的位置
They were very attuned into its location.
你只在乎自己 是吗
So you're only out for yourself, huh?
都为了你自己
It's all about number one?
做猎人就高尚得多吗
Being a hunter is so much more noble?
一群执迷于复仇的反社会
Bunch of obsessed, revenge-driven sociopaths.
努力拯救无法被拯救的世界
trying to save a world that can't be saved?
你还真是乐观呢
Well, aren't you a glass half full?
我们都要下地狱 迪恩
We're all going to hell, Dean.
不如享受一番
Might as well enjoy the ride.
这我倒是同意
I actually agree with you there.
反正 聊得愉快 但是
Anyhoo, this has been charming, but,
看这都几点了
look at the time.
对了 这个
And this?
看来你不是唯一手脚不干净的
Looks like you're not the only one with sticky fingers.
如果能让你好受点 我觉得你真是个烂人
If it's any consolation, I think you're a truly awful person.
回见
See you.
你参与了恶魔打开魔鬼之门的计划 是吧
You were part of that demon plan to open the gate, weren't you?
我们尽全力阻止了
We did everything we could to stop it.
撒谎
Lie, lie, lie.
你跟他们是一伙儿的
You were in on it.
你还知道他们的下一步计划吧
You know what their next move is, too, don't you?
不 我不知道 你全搞错了
No, I don't, okay? You're wrong about all of this.
他们接下来要袭击哪里
Where are they gonna hit us next?
哪里
Where?
戈登跟我说了你 萨姆
Gordon told me about you, Sam.
说了你的能力
About your powers.
你是个奇怪的灵力怪物
You're some kind of weirdo, psychic freak.
不 现在不是了 我没有能力 没有幻视了
No, not anymore. I have no powers, no visions.
- 什么都没了 - 撒谎
- Nothing. It's just… - Lie.
别再撒谎了
Now, no more lies.
现在外面有一支恶魔大军
There's an army of demons out there,
摧残着一个本就处于崩溃边缘的世界
pushing at a world already on the brink.
我们即将迎来终局 是吧
We're on deck for the end game here, right?
那或许
So maybe,
或许 你能理解
just maybe, you can understand…
我们为何不能冒险
why we can't take chances.
- 好吧 等一下的 - 库布里克
- Okay. Okay, now, hold on a minute. - Kubrick…
不 你什么都看到了 克雷迪
No. You saw what happened, Creedy.
你自己想想 我们为什么会在这里
Ask yourself, why are we here?
因为你看到了网站上的一张照片吗
Because you saw a picture on the web?
因为我们选择了这家旅馆 而不是另一家吗
Because we chose this motel instead of another?
那种运气不会凭空出现
Luck like that doesn't just happen.
- 这我都能解释 你… - 闭嘴
- Look, I can explain all of that if… - Shut up.
是上帝 克雷迪
It's God, Creedy.
他指引我们来这里只有一个原因
He led us here for one reason.
行他的工作
To do his work.
这是命运
This is destiny.
不 不是命运
Nope. No destiny.
只是个兔脚
Just a rabbit's foot.
放下枪 小子
Put the gun down, son…
不然等着擦墙上的脑浆吧
or you're gonna be scraping brain off the wall.
这个吗
This thing?
对 就那个
Yeah, that thing.
好吧
Okay.
但是 有件关于我的事你不知道
But you see, there's something about me that you don't know.
是吗 什么事
Yeah, what would that be?
今天我走运
It's my lucky day.
天啊 你看到了吗
My God. Did you see that shot?
我太厉害了
I'm amazing.
我是蝙蝠侠
I'm Batman.
嗯
Yeah.
你是蝙蝠侠
You're Batman.
好了
All right.
骨灰 卡宴辣椒
Bone ash. Cayenne pepper.
应该可以了
That should do it.
稍等
One second.
迪恩
Dean…
少来 霉鬼 看我行大运
Back off, jinx. Bringing home the bacon.
好了
All right.
再见吧 坏兔子
Say goodbye, rascally rabbit.
我想你会发现那是我的
I think you'll find that belongs to me.
或者…随便了
Or, you know, whatever.
把兔脚放下 亲爱的
Put the foot down, honey.
不
No.
你不会开枪的
You're not gonna shoot anybody.
我这人会识人
See, I happen to be able to read people.
好吧 你是个贼 但你不…
Okay, you're a thief, fine, but you're not…
- 该死 - 别过来 猛男
- Son of a… - Back off, tiger.
别过来
Back off.
你再动一下 我就扣扳机
You make one more move and I'll pull the trigger.
你有运气 迪恩 我打不中你
You've got the luck, Dean. You I can't hit.
但你弟弟
But your brother?
我打不偏
Him I can't miss.
你有什么毛病
What the hell is wrong with you?
你怎么能随便这么冲人开枪
You don't just go around shooting people like that.
放松
Relax.
只是打了肩 我会瞄准的
It's a shoulder hit. I can aim.
再说 这里谁没冲人开过枪呢
Besides, who here hasn't shot a few people?
马上把兔脚放地上
Put the rabbit's foot on the ground now.
好吧
All right. All right.
别激动
Just take it easy.
反应快
Think fast.
该死
Damn.
好了
Now,
我们把那破玩意销毁掉怎么样
what do you say we destroy that ugly-ass piece of dead thing?
多谢了
Thanks very much.
我丢了150万美元
I'm out one-and-a-half million.
还惹到了一个很有权势的疯子买家
and on the bad side of a powerful, fairly psychotic buyer.
我一点不为此感到不安呢 萨姆
I really don't feel bad about that. Sam?
我也不
Nope.
完全不呢
Not even a little.
或许下次 会是我对你不管不顾
Maybe next time, I'll hang you out to dry.
别气冲冲地离开 离开就行
Don't go away angry. Just go away.
祝你们晚上愉快 小伙子们
Have a nice night, boys.
你没事吧
You good?
死不了
I'll live.
看来我们回归正常了 是吧
I guess we're back to normal now, huh?
没有好运 没有厄运
No good luck, no bad luck.
差点忘了 我们赢了4.6万美元了
Forgot, we're up $46, 000.
差点忘了那些…
I almost forgot about the…
刮刮乐
scratch tickets.
该死
Son of a bitch!
你全都说对了
You were right about everything.
萨姆·温彻斯特不是单纯的怪物
Sam Winchester is more than a monster.
他是敌人
He's the adversary.
你为什么相信了
And what was it that convinced you?
上帝指引我找到了他
God led me to him.
他的旨意很明确
And his will is clear.
好吧
Okay.
太好了
That's great.
很高兴你也看清了事实
Glad to have you onboard.
但先做要紧事
But, uh, first things first.
我们得想办法帮我越狱
We gotta get me the hell out of here.
因为就像我之前跟你说的
Because like I told you before…
萨姆·温彻斯特必须死
Sam Winchester must die.